cgcookie.com 2014-12-02

# Privacy Policy - CG Cookie

**Privacy Policy CG Cookie, Inc and it’s Network of site[http://blendercookie.com](http://blendercookie.com/), [http://maxcookie.com](http://maxcookie.com/), [https://cgcookie.com](https://cgcookie.com/), [http://modocookie.com](http://modocookie.com/), [http://unitycookie.com](http://unitycookie.com/), [http://conceptcookie.com](http://unitycookie.com/), [http://workshops.cgcookie.com](http://workshops.cgcookie.com/). Effective and Last Updated: April 16th, 2014**

This website is owned and operated by CG Cookie, Inc. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors while they interact with the content, products and services on this site (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy applies to this site and CG Cookie, Inc owned sites only. It does not apply to other websites to which we link to. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want you to understand what information we collect about you, how we collect it, how that information is used, and how you can control our disclosure of it. You agree that your use of the Site signifies your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

**1) Information Collected**. We collect two types of information from you: i) information that you voluntarily provide to us (e.g. through a voluntary registration process, sign-ups or emails); and ii) information that is derived through automated tracking mechanisms.

### Voluntary Registration Information.

> In order to fully access this Site, you must first complete the registration process, during which we will collect personal information about you. The information will include your name, phone, address, and email address. We do not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically provide such information to us on a voluntary basis. By registering with us, you consent to the use and method of disclosure as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Voluntary Information for Services and Features.

> We [also] collect personally identifiable information when you choose to use certain other features of the Site, including: i) making purchases, ii) consenting to receive email, iii) participating in our forum, iv) commenting on articles, and others. When you choose to use these additional features, we require you to provide your “Contact Information” in addition to other personal information that may be required to complete a transaction such as your phone number, billing and shipping addresses and minimal payment information. (such as Paypal E-mail address or Google Checkout) CG Cookie, Inc does NOT store any actual payment, Credit Card, or Bank information. Occasionally, we may also request information such as your shopping preferences and demographics which will help us better serve you and our others users in the future.

### Cookies

> Our site uses “cookies” and other tracking technologies. Cookies enable us to serve secure pages to our users without asking them to sign in repeatedly. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. If a user’s system is idle for a defined time, the cookie will expire, forcing the user to sign in again to continue their session. This prevents unauthorized access to the user’s information while they are away from their computer. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Site.

### Google Adwords

This website uses the [Google AdWords](http://www.google.com/ads/adwords/) remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example signing up for a trial of the Tradevine product. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the [Google Display Network](http://www.google.com/ads/displaynetwork/). Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the CG Cookie website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Preferences page](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want to you can [opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or [permanently using a browser plugin](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/).

**2) Referrals** You may choose to invite friends to join the **CG Cookie** by sending invitation emails via our invite feature. **CG Cookie** stores the email addresses you provide so that the respondents may be added to your social network, confirm orders/purchases and also to send reminders of the invitations. **CG Cookie** does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders. Recipients of invitations may contact **CG Cookie** to request removal of their information from our database.

**3) How We Use Your Information CG Cookie** only uses your personal information for the original purposes it was given. **Your personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without your approval at the time of collection**. **CG Cookie** will not disclose, use, give or sell any personal information to third parties for any purposes other than to our suppliers and other third parties who need to know in order to deliver services on behalf of **CG Cookie** unless required to do so by law. Further, **CG Cookie** reserves the right to contact you regarding matters relevant to the underlying service provided and/or the information collected. Please note that personally identifiable information is used only to provide you with a more enjoyable, convenient online experience and to help us identify and/or provide information, products or services that may be of interest to you. We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features, including without limitation: fulfilling your order; providing customer service; tracking email invitations you send; and otherwise supporting your use of the Site. **CG Cookie** may use your personal information for target advertising toward you based on things such as region, gender, interests, goals, habits, etc. We may permit certain trusted third parties to track usage, analyze data such as the source address that a page request is coming from, your IP address or domain name, the date and time of the page request, the referring Web site (if any) and other parameters in the URL. This is collected in order to better understand our Web site usage, and enhance the performance of services to maintain and operate the Site and certain features on the Site. We may use third parties to host the Site; operate various features available on the Site; send emails; analyze data; provide search results and links and assist in fulfilling your orders. Also, we may share personally identifiable or other information with our parent, subsidiaries, divisions, and affiliates. We may transfer personally identifiable information as an asset in connection with a proposed or actual merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control. **CG Cookie** may disclose Contact Information in special cases where we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms and conditions of use or may be causing injury or interference with our rights, property, our customers or anyone who could be harmed by such activities. WE ARE NOT LIABLE OR RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE OR OTHER INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE TO SUBMIT IN FORUMS SUCH AS A BULLETIN BOARD, COMMENT SECTION, CHAT ROOM OR ANY OTHER PUBLICLY ACCESSIBLE AREA OF THE SITE. You will receive notice when your personally identifiable information might be provided to any third party for any reason other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, and you will have an opportunity to request that we not share such information. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and for business and administrative purposes. We may also use or share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that contains no personally identifiable information.

**4)** **How We Protect Your Information.** We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We take appropriate security measures to protect your information against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we maintain appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information and data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

Advertisements appearing on this Site may be delivered to you by **CG Cookie** or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies.

**5) Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences** We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personal information for many of our services. You may modify or remove any of your personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing features such as edit and account.

**6) Site Notifications/Opt-out** If you no longer wish to receive updates or notifications may opt-out of receiving these communications by changing your “notifications” settings in your “dashboard settings.”

**7) Disclaimer to Security**  
By consenting to the Terms and Conditions of the Site and hence the Privacy Policy, you consent that no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. We cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you provide to us and you transmit such information to us at your own risk.

**8 ) Notification of Changes**  
**CG Cookie** reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. If at some point in the future, there is a change to our Privacy Policy, unless we obtain your express consent, such change will only apply to information collected after the revised Privacy Policy took effect. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.

**9) CONTACT INFORMATION:** If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy please contact:

CG Cookie, Inc  
support@cgcookie.com  
27 W. State Street, STE B  
Geneva IL 60134
